npros.com 2005-12-12

# Privacy Policy

|  |  |  | 

**Privacy Policy**

**Collection of information**  
When you visit our website, we do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. If you decide to register for our leads, or if you request information from us, you will be asked to provide basic contact information, including your name and email e-mail address. The information you provide helps us create customized content. 

Our system also logs some basic and generic information about your computer, including its:

• IP address (your computer's unique signature)  
• Operating system (e.g. Windows NT)  
• Browser software (e.g. Netscape Navigator)

We use this information about your computer to perform routine web site maintenance and to generate various aggregate reports for internal analysis, research and monitoring purposes, so as to help us develop and enhance our web site and services for our users.

**Npros respects your privacy**  
We will not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information about our users to other parties, without our users' consent. 

We do not distribute or share our information with anyone. Period.

We do reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases, for example, when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), our title, rights, interests or property, or those of other web site users, or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose, with notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement, or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority. 

**  
Use of information**  
We may use the information you provide to respond to your requests for additional information, to contact you, if necessary, to service your account or for other administrative purposes. We may also access your information to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to enforce agreements between us, or for marketing purposes - but only if you have granted us permission to send you leads or marketing material. In addition, for certain transactions, our system may use your transaction details to automate and to streamline your transaction by checking for electronic data compliance, providing reporting features, and transferring data from previous forms to those of the current transaction. 

**NOTICE TO SPAMMERS**  
Npros will gladly read any "SPAM" or marketing emails you send to an address you manually or electronically lift from our site, for a one time reading fee of $100.00 (one hundred dollars). We will provide you with a short but concise evaluation of your spam email in advance of your $100 evaluation fee. We will email the evaluation to the reply address listed on the spam you send us for evaluation, unless you notify us in writing at our mailing address that you wish the evaluation sent to an alternative address. We are not responsible for erroneous email addresses you may have listed with domain registration agencies. If you believe your email address may be in error, do not send us spam as per this agreemen, unless we are notified, we will complete the evaluation and reply to the address given in your spam message. By emailing us any promotional message not meant as a non-commercial communication between a private, individual party and the administrators of this site, or any commercial or promotional message the content of which is specifically targeted at generating click, traffic, or sale of a product or servicec, you accept the terms of this agreement. Npros does not, and has never "opted in" to your or your "partner" site, posted a message on your message board, or in any other way provided our email address to you as an interested party in your spam messages. Messages sent will be solely through intentionally lifting our email address from our copyrighted content on pages on this site, and under the specific terms of this agreement. Anyone who sends us spam will receive a bill by mail to the address listed on the domain registration. Payments not received within 30 days will be subject to collection action to the full extent of the applicable law, including but not limited to small claims action and filing of liens in the event a judgement is not satisfied. We want to thank all Spammers and their automated spider software for the opportunity to do business with you, and look forward to profitable business and/or collection actions against you in the future.Send SPAM for review under the terms of this agreement to BILLMEFORREADINGTHIS@NPROS.COM

©Npros.com 1999-2003  

|  |  |   |
